♪♪♪
♪ WELCOME TO NELLYVILLE ♪
♪ WHERE ALL NEWBORNS
GET A HALF-A-MILL' ♪
♪ SONS GET SEDAN DEVILLES ♪
♪ SOON AS THEY CAN
REACH THE WHEEL ♪
♪ AND DAUGHTERS GET DIAMONDS
THE SIZE OF THEIR AGE ♪
♪ I'M TALKIN' ONE
YEAR GET ONE CARAT ♪
♪ TWO YEARS GET TWO CARATS ♪
♪♪♪
♪ I LOVE YOU, AND I NEED YOU ♪
♪ NELLY I LOVE YOU,
I DO NEED YOU ♪
♪ NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
ALL I THINK ABOUT IS YOU ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN I'M WITH MY BOO ♪
♪ BOY, YOU KNOW I'M
CRAZY OVER YOU ♪
♪ NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
ALL I THINK ABOUT IS YOU ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN I'M WITH MY BOO ♪
♪ YOU KNOW I'M CRAZY OVER YOU ♪
♪ I MET THIS CHICK ♪
♪ AND SHE JUST MOVED RIGHT
UP THE BLOCK FROM ME ♪
♪ AND UH, SHE GOT
THE HOTS FOR ME ♪
♪ THE FINEST THING
MY HOOD DONE SEEN ♪
♪ BUT OH NO, OH NO,
SHE GOTTA A MAN ♪
♪ AND A SON, THOUGH,
BUT THAT'S OKAY ♪
♪ CAUSE I WAIT FOR MY CUE AND
JUST LISTEN, PLAY MY POSITION ♪
♪ LIKE A SHORTSTOP, PICK UP
EVERYTHING MAMI HITTIN' ♪
♪ AND IN NO TIME ♪
♪ I PLAN TO MAKE
THIS ONE HERE MINE ♪
♪ AND THAT'S FOR SURE ♪
♪ CAUSE I, I NEVER BEEN THE
TYPE TO BREAK UP A HAPPY HOME ♪
♪ BUT UH, THERE'S
SOMETHING BOUT BABY GIRL ♪
♪ I JUST CAN'T LEAVE ALONE ♪
♪ SO TELL ME MA WHAT'S
IT GONNA BE, SHE SAID ♪
♪ YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN TO ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
ALL I THINK ABOUT IS YOU ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN I'M WITH MY BOO ♪
♪ BOY, YOU KNOW I'M
CRAZY OVER YOU ♪
♪ NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
ALL I THINK ABOUT IS YOU ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN I'M WITH MY BOO,
YOU KNOW I'M CRAZY OVER YOU ♪
♪ I SEE YOU A LOT AND YOU
LOOK AND I NEVER SAY A WORD ♪
♪ I KNOW HOW START
ACTIN TRIPPIN' OUT
HERE ABOUT THEY GIRLS ♪
♪ AND THERE'S NO WAY
NELLY GON' FIGHT OVER ♪
♪ NO DAME AS YOU CAN SEE ♪
♪ BUT I, I LIKE YOUR STEEZ, YOUR
STYLE, YOUR WHOLE DEMEANOR ♪
♪ THE WAY YOU COME
THROUGH AND HOLLA ♪
♪ AND SWOOP ME IN
HIS TWO-SEATER ♪
♪ NOW THAT'S GANGSTA ♪
♪ AND I GOT SPECIAL
WAYS TO THANK YA ♪
♪ DON'T YOU FORGET IT ♪
♪ BUT UH, IT AIN'T THAT EASY
FOR YOU TO PACK AND LEAVE HIM ♪
♪ BUT UH, YOU AND DIRTY GOT
TIES FOR DIFFERENT REASONS ♪
♪ I RESPECT THAT AND
RIGHT BEFORE I TURN
TO LEAVE, SHE SAID ♪
♪ YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN TO ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
ALL I THINK ABOUT IS YOU ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN I'M WITH MY BOO ♪
♪ BOY, YOU KNOW I'M
CRAZY OVER YOU ♪
♪ NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
ALL I THINK ABOUT IS YOU ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN I'M WITH MY BOO,
YOU KNOW I'M CRAZY OVER YOU ♪
♪ SING IT FOR ME, K ♪
♪ AND I LOVE YOU,
AND I NEED YOU ♪
♪ NELLY I LOVE YOU, I DO ♪
♪ C'MON GIRL ♪
♪ AND IT'S MORE THAN
YOU'LL EVER KNOW ♪
♪ BOY, IT'S FOR SURE ♪
♪ YOU CAN ALWAYS
COUNT ON MY LOVE ♪
♪ FOREVER MORE, YEAH, YEAH ♪
♪ EAST COAST, I KNOW
YOU SHAKIN' RIGHT ♪
♪ DOWN SOUTH, I KNOW
YOU BOUNCIN' RIGHT ♪
♪ WEST COAST, I KNOW YOU
WALKIN' RIGHT, CAUSE ♪
♪ YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN TO ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
ALL I THINK ABOUT IS YOU ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN I'M WITH MY BOO ♪
♪ BOY, YOU KNOW I'M
CRAZY OVER YOU ♪
♪ NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
ALL I THINK ABOUT IS YOU ♪
♪ EVEN WHEN I'M WITH MY BOO,
YOU KNOW I'M CRAZY OVER YOU ♪
♪ EAST COAST, I KNOW
YOU SHAKIN' RIGHT ♪
♪ DOWN SOUTH, I KNOW
YOU BOUNCIN' RIGHT ♪
♪ WEST COAST, I KNOW YOU
WALKIN' RIGHT, CAUSE ♪
♪ YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN TO ME ♪
♪ EAST COAST, YOU
STILL SHAKIN' RIGHT ♪
♪ DOWN SOUTH, I SEE
YOU BOUNCIN' RIGHT ♪
♪ WEST COAST, I KNOW YOU
WALKIN' RIGHT, CAUSE ♪
♪ YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN TO ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER WHAT I DO ♪
- KELLY! KELLY BRING
YOUR BUTT UP HERE NOW!
YOU BETTER COME ON HERE GIRL!
I AINT PLAYING WITH
YOU NOW, COME ON.
COME ON NOW, RIGHT
NOW! KELLY, KELLY!